Hey guys, um Pastor Meyers here. Um
I am just jumping on uh quickly to
make an announcement uh for those of you
that have signed up for the Daniel in 7
days class. Um, we were um scheduled to
start it today,
but um I am actually still out of town.
I'm actually in Virginia and I'm going
to be flying back uh to uh Huntsville
today. So, um I'll be in the air at the
time our class was supposed to start
because I was supposed to leave earlier
and because of flight delays and weather
um wasn't able to to um to get back home
in time. So,
um I'm just letting you know that the
Daniel in 7 days class will start
tomorrow night. Okay. Um for those of
you that are in my photo theology class,
we'll still be doing photo theology
tomorrow night, but we'll be doing it at
6:00 p.m. So, 6:00 p.m. to 7:00 p.m.
Central Standard Time. And then at se
from 7 to 9 will be the uh Daniel and 7
days class. For those of you in my
apologetics class, we will be doing
class Tuesday. Um, but we're going to
move it up an hour. So, that class will
be 6 pm as well, 6 p.m. to 7. And then
the Daniel uh in 7 days class will begin
at 7 uh and go to 9:00. So,
if you wanted to sign up for the class,
you have an extra day. So uh the the
website once again is
myphototheology.com
and you will see the Daniel in 7 days
course and you will also see the
revelation in 7 days course that begins
uh next Sunday. So again guys this this
Daniel and Revelation course is uh is
unlike uh any other course.
Um, you will not just be learning the
what, but you will be learning the why.
Okay. Um, very powerful study. You will
not regret it if you take this class.
Promise you. Um, all right y'all, that's
it. Just wanted to again jump on and
make that quick announcement. And so,
um, I look forward to seeing you all in
class tomorrow night. And uh be prepared
uh be prepared to understand the book
like you never have before. All right,
y'all. Peace.